evliving.com 2010-12-30

# Privacy Policy | Phoenix Arizona Real Estate Local News and Business Directory

Browse >

[Home](http://www.evliving.com/ "Browse to: Home") / Privacy Policy 

Published By Editor

EVLiving.com takes your privacy seriously.  Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

**What This Privacy Policy Covers**

This policy covers how EVLiving.com treats personal information that EVLiving.com collects and receives, including information related to prior use of EVLiving.com products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that EVLiving.com does not own or control, or to people that EVLiving.com does not employ or manage.

**Information Collection and Use**

General

EVLiving.com collects personal information when you register with EVLiving.com, when you use EVLiving.com products or services, when you visit EVLiving.com pages or the pages of certain EVLiving.com partners, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes. EVLiving.com may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies.

When you register we may ask for information such as your name, email address,  zip code, or personal interests.  Once you register with EVLiving.com and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.

EVLiving.com uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.

Children 

When a child under age 13 attempts to register with EVLiving.com, we ask that he or she have a parent or guardian create a EVLiving.com Family Account to obtain parental permission.

EVLiving.com will not contact children under age 13 about special offers or for marketing purposes without a parent’s permission.

EVLiving.com does not ask a child under age 13 for more personal information, as a condition of participation, than is reasonably necessary to participate in a given activity or promotion.

Information Sharing and Disclosure 

EVLiving.com does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you’ve requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with EVLiving.com under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help EVLiving.com communicate with you about offers from EVLiving.com and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.

We have a parent’s permission to share the information if the user is a child under age 13. Parents have the option of allowing EVLiving.com to collect and use their child’s information without consenting to EVLiving.com sharing of this information with people and companies who may use this information for their own purposes;

We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;

We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of EVLiving.com’s terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

We transfer information about you if EVLiving.com is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, EVLiving.com will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

EVLiving.com displays targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click on targeted ads meet the targeting criteria – for example, women ages 18-24 from a particular geographic area.

EVLiving.com does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad.

EVLiving.com advertisers include financial service providers (such as banks, insurance agents, stock brokers and mortgage lenders) and non-financial companies (such as stores, airlines, and software companies).

**Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences**

General 

You can edit your EVLiving.com Account Information, including your marketing preferences, at any time.

New categories of marketing communications may be added to the Marketing Preferences page from time to time. Users who visit this page can opt out of receiving future marketing communications from these new categories or they can unsubscribe by following instructions contained in the messages they receive.

Certain communications from EVLiving.com, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the EVLiving.com Newsletter, are considered part of EVLiving.com membership and you may not opt out of receiving them.

You can delete your EVLiving.com account by sending us a please delete my account email.

Children

Parents can review, edit, and delete information relating to their child’s EVLiving.com account using tools offered by EVLiving.com Family Accounts.

If a parent chooses not to allow us to further collect or use a child’s information, parents enrolled in EVLiving.com Family Accounts can delete their child’s account by sending us email.

Confidentiality and Security 

We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.

We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you.

Your EVLiving.com Account Information is password-protected.

In certain areas EVLiving.com uses industry-standard SSL encryption to protect data transmissions.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

EVLiving.com may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your EVLiving.com account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

**Questions and Suggestions**

If you have questions or suggestions, please let us know by sending an email to **[Business Office](mailto:info@evliving.com)**.

Please enjoy the site.

**Addendum for Interest Based Advertising**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).
